because the market is indeed very strong
so talking about gainers uh you've got a
dish also up about 10 those are really
the stocks of the morning
apart from that a couple of these larger
mid caps when we guard and couple of
these other stocks have started the day
on a pretty uh positive note media in
general by the way even sun tv tv 18
broadcast a disclaimer of course there
that is the company that owns and
operates the channel that you're
watching a lot of media stocks are
actually doing pretty well to start the
session off with uh so that's how it's
opening up the mid cap market the mid
cap index up about a half a percent so
is the bank nifty and the nifty is
sitting pretty with a gain of about 54
points so i know
at opening i mean
i mean today it's not about i think one
big stock moving the index it seems to
be a larger basket that's generally
taking things out you know oh absolutely
you know you hit the nail on the head
there's not too many stocks up more than
one percent still the index is up about
55 points so you know the issue is
always this you know when you get so
close to all-time high uh there's always
this algo profit taking program profit
taking now has that already happened in
the market making a fresh move i don't
know we'll find out i think you could
also focus on individual names mid caps
doing well a lot of stocks doing well of
course z is doing well
uh
the other media stocks on tv pv are
doing well keep an eye on india mart
that corrected for two days and today
it's you see in the the breakaway gap
with open as low so that could be an
interesting stock to track uh so you
know you'll have to look at individual
stocks perhaps uh
if nifty is not your cup of tea but with
your thoughts on the index or any
individual stock that you may have
tracked
well no job you know the uh nifty as i
said i think i'm waiting for this
earlier high to be cleared i think
there's a good chance we will do that
and once that happens uh with a 40 point
kind of a stop a trade can be taken
uh on the stock side i think you know uh
early in the morning uh would look at uh
access bank i think that's reversing on
the hourly charts after correcting from
eight one fight about 785 is now showing
signs of reversal so could be a good bet
to take long trades keep your stock
below 785 and look at a target of around
eight one five to begin with okay mitesh
thanks a lot for for joining us
joining us now ceo of nirvang
institutional equities
uh rahul good morning thanks for joining
us
before we talk about the market i wanted
your thoughts on z if you track the
developments and uh whether you know
you know how would you approach this
talk now
morning thanks for having me on so uh
unfortunately no official coverage on z
but obviously i think the news has been
taken very positively by the market i
think uh if you just look at the stock
standalone some of their properties have
started to do really well off late so i
think uh they could do with some amount
of change and some fresh thinking but uh
as a standard disclaimer don't track the
stock but definitely i mean it's if
you're
holding the stock i would on the back of
the news that is coming overnight i
would definitely continue holding it
okay uh rahul morning
i want to talk to you about autos
because if there's disruption that's
really played out for one reason or the
other it's in that side of the market
right a lot of the major oems continue
to struggle do you see the present
situation as a you know buy in
opportunity or is this a disruption for
the long haul so best avoided
uh morning survey so i think uh you know
the biggest issue plaguing the industry
is the semiconductor issue uh and you
know we've been doing a lot of study and
you're sort of hosting a lot of experts
that are working out trying to
understand this and uh it seems like
this is a transient issue i don't think
anyone can put a lid on exactly when
this problem would resolve itself uh but
if you look at the global semiconductor
companies uh survey they are actually
their capex for the next one year is
actually higher than it was in the
pre-covered era by at least 15 to 20 and
this is a study that we recently put out
which is uh quite astounding so i think
once this issue does resolve itself uh
in six months or a year from now uh in
totality i think uh you know this
particular issue will be put to bed the
issue then will probably go back to
demand and i think in the backdrop of
the monsoon that we're having and the
kind of commentary that we've seen from
tractor vehicles as well as commercial
vehicles i think at least that part of
the market seems to be in a cyclical
upswing uh at our broken house we're
still very sanguine about names like
ashok leyland and the auto financers on
the cv side and even tractor players
like mahendra and mahindra
on the two wheeler side i think
obviously the big talk has been about
eevees and you know trying to find the
best place of the three or four listed
two wheeler players on the eevee side
i think uh given the charging
infrastructure in the company again it's
a slightly long haul but i think pbs is
probably the best place according to us
uh in that bracket and of course if you
want to play passenger vehicles martha
is pretty much the only proxy so i think
most of the issues are transients and
you know more medium term issues but i
think once you tied over them uh some of
these names like i said ashok leyland
uh eminem tvs maruti could still be very
good portfolio holes for the long term
okay good portfolio holds in the auto
space uh given the rising electric
vehicle trend but i wanted your thoughts
rahul by the way good morning and thanks
for being with us on the channel i
wanted your thoughts on irctc i mean
this entire unlocked trade is playing
out beautifully and now some of these
stocks are hitting fresh highs
uh the stock has has risen so much from
its you know its ipo days
do you still see more up moves here or
do you think this this story has played
out in its entirety
for a lot of these names uh sonia it's
been a bit of a dream run i mean irctc
is the case in point i mean take a look
at concord as another example you know
and there's this entire top of this
investment so i think a lot of these
themes have played out pretty well uh
these are very marquee names and some of
these are either in a monopoly or a
duopoly in terms of you know
their clientele and the kind of revenue
streams that they have so i think if you
were a shareholder in some names like
irctc or concord
and you've seen the returns that you
have i don't see any reason to sell out
i mean sometimes you know you don't
necessarily need to take profits just
because the stock has done well if it's
going to continue to compound for you at
fifteen twenty percent so uh if i was a
holder in names uh like the ones that
you mentioned i would probably still
continue to be long-term holders i think
these are these are portfolio names
these are not really names that you
trade and trade out and look at uh you
know uh short-term data so i think you
know when you look at the order books of
most of these companies in the order
book stupid ratio uh and the fact like i
said that they are probably one or two
of the players in their industry that
are you know taking away market share
and are growing their revenues
incrementally i see no specific reason
to be taking profits at any point in
time i mean portfolio holds for me for
sure
okay by the way uh that's ten percent
freeze opened on z and didn't last for
too long it's now on fifteen percent
uh freeze so uh you know uh fn stock so
just to reiterate uh uh
that's the staircase kind of formation
that you know uh can happen on stocks
like z once the once the circuit opens
so uh let's see if uh you know how that
one pans out but for now having uh a
good day right now but uh rahul you used
to track some of these uh you know tn
coffee stocks uh my memory serves me
right you know names like ccl
and you know even tata coffee etc
any thoughts here these stocks have made
a big comeback
uh i know cc has been a stock i think
we've looked at since the price was 50
rupees a few years back we continue to
remain very positive obviously the
moving parts on a name like ccl have
changed
uh you know from where it started off
being a coffee converter uh and you know
sort of supplying to major major global
oems on a real-time basis to branding
out into you know their own particular
brand continental coffee
and into other markets like vietnam
switzerland and the united states so uh
we remain sanguine which i think uh this
is potentially uh and i'll choose my
words a bit carefully uh if the issues
that have plagued them during the
lockdown uh with respect to you know ho
chi minh city for example being in
lockdown for a better part of the last
few months and the issues that they had
with the container availability in india
and of course the russia issue yeah if
all of these issues resolve themselves
over six months to a year i think the
stock is still a potential doubler even
from here uh it's one of those very few
consumer stocks that give you uh the
kind of valuations i don't think it's
trading at north of 20 times
on a one year forward yet and the return
ratios are in the early 20s uh this is
practically a debt-free company it does
give you very strong operating cash
flows uh you know and their continental
brand is doing pretty well not just in
the private sector but even in the
public sector you get these in the army
canteens you get them on the rajasthanis
and the
of the world so while their global
markets are you know opening up and
india is sort of you know also doing
well for them the branded coffee market
is also picking up in a very substantial
way and i think over the last two years
i know they've added two or three very
marquee clients uh to their legacy
business so my sense is there are very
few companies in the coffee or in the
consumer sector i would call it
complete on the consumer sector that are
coming to you about the valuations that
this particular company is so i would
not be surprised if in the next two or
three years that this stock actually
even doubles from here i remember the
conversation with the management earlier
this month and they're talking about
vietnam that huge expansion that's
underway over there
tea coffee brings me to food rahul no we
know your love for west life but my
question is actually more on zamato
how did you process their decision not
to get into grocery delivery uh and they
i think right now i wanted to stay
focused on uh
you know the dining business as well as
of course overall food delivery how do
you look at the stock
uh it's actually a very big positive for
the way i look at it because you know
you have global giants and even indian
giants that are present in that
particular space and obviously they have
the investment in growth that they do to
uh to leverage that so i you know
i mean somato for example even has taken
a license or is in the process of
applying for a license for payments uh
so i'm not sure how that's going to pan
out but i think a lot of these platform
companies should be over a period of
time will try and branch out from their
core into other avenues to try and
leverage their existing customer base
it's not an improvement strategy but you
will have to see the competitive
landscape before you get in and since
you bought a food i can just reference
this for example uh to a qsr player like
jubilant food works who branched out
from pizzas into chinese and biryani so
you expand your platform and it's only
natural
once you see some amount of you know
number of customers that you've got on
your
on your platform and you want to
leverage that on on multiple particular
revenue streams so i think from a
capital allocation standpoint uh a good
strategy because i would like to see
zomato at least deliver for three or
four quarters on their numbers on the
existing business uh before they take
any moves like that i still personally
believe that the stock is very very
overvalued if you look at it from a one
term a one year perspective i know a lot
of my peers and larger peers have come
up with buy reports from this stock uh
and
you know it's it's always good to dread
with caution now you know so i tell
people very often that when i used to
look at real estate as a sector in 2008
to 10 a lot of companies that have
projected profits for dlf two or three
years out that company has never done
sales of that amount in a particular
financial year so
some amount of exuberance in a new
sector in the market uh will always be
there in the early 2000s it was the it
sector at the end of the last decade or
early beginning of this decade it was
real estate now it's fintech and
platforms but yeah to your specific
question i think from a capital
allocation standpoint a good move but uh
you know let's see how the tomato story
plays out so we i think you know i think
it's a test of institutional investors
as well i mean it is a loss-making
company at some stage uh the mindset is
very different from private equity they
are going to ask for arrows and rocs
eventually so they're giving it the
benefit of doubt uh if you're holding it
hold on i think you'll still make some
money but
i'll be watching this space very very
carefully
okay and one more space very quickly
before we run out of time rahul is the
entire speciality chemical space right i
mean srf has been hitting new highs
deepak nitrite lakshmi organics you name
it and that whole gamut has looked good
what would your pick up the pack be
where there is still some valuation
headroom and growth potential
well if you were an srf shareholder you
were very happy a few days back one day
when you got those four bonus shares for
every one that you were holding but it
remains one of our top large cap picks
sonia on the chemical side i think srf
is definitely a portfolio hold i think
it's it's uh it's doing the right things
but i think it would still not be the
topic we would have in campus my topic
would still be naveen floating as a
house obviously they're doing what they
are on the fluorination side of the
business but i think their
diversification into the cram side of
the business
uh is a very interesting one uh the
market has ascribed some amount of
option value to the crime side of the
business and uh sonia we've actually
studied uh some global companies that
have been in chemicals and fluorination
and very similar kinds of businesses to
naveen florin that have branched out
into similar lines of businesses like
crams uh what we figured is that the
first hundred million dollars of
revenues on the gram side of the
business typically takes anywhere
between three to five years uh but once
the clients are locked in the
incremental hundred million dollars
revenue come in very very quickly and at
very high margins uh and the margins
actually go up progressively as the
years go by so the profitability of
companies like these can actually grow
very disproportionately if they actually
hit the bullseye so if you look at
naveen florian on a standalone basis
you'll probably find it very difficult
to justify but i think it's if you look
at it as a pharma company with option
value that you know a few drugs could go
right i think this could still be a
stock that would compound compound
anywhere between 20 to 25 percent for
you so again a very well held stock on
the institutional side but i see no
reason uh why people can't make an entry
into the stock if they have a two
three-year horizon so this would be our
topic from the uh on the larger uh you
know srf and naveen florian in larger
chemical space and if you want to go
down the value chain into speciality
ingredients then we would say look at
something like a fine organics that
looks a little interesting to us
or even something like a camel and fine
sciences
one last question since you've tracked
the stock sbi live post that block it's
sort of underperformed rahul but uh
would you buy it here
uh it's a very interesting question uh
anuj uh look i think max life sbi live
and icse life are all trading at very
similar valuations on which and all
these three valuations are about 2.6 to
2.9 times price to embedded value
compared to an hdfc life of what north
of four times while we are very very
positive on the insurance space our
topic there would be icsa potential life
insurance purely because the business
mix has so dramatically changed from the
ulip side to traditional insurance and
you've seen that in the vmp margins sbi
life again a great portfolio hold i
would definitely buy it but our pecking
order insurance right now onwards would
be icici pro-life one max life two uh
probably uh hdfc live at the bottom of
the pack and sbi life would probably be
third in that pecking order
okay got that raul appreciate you
joining us on the show today thanks very
much for taking up the time you have a
good day and we look forward to our next